# **TUDOR POPESCU**

## JUNIOR UX DESIGNER

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

A strong personal affinity for music and 2 years' experience working in the music, entertainment and web3 space as a freelance Junior UX/UI Designer. I thrive in a collaborative team environment and have experience working with front-end developers and project managers delivering design handoffs that include layout parameters, image assets, directions for user interactions and animations. Key experience includes designing mobile app interfaces, building a web game, updating and maintaining a shared design library.

My most enjoyable project involved designing a game UI dedicated to helping non-musicians and primary school students learn music in a fun group environment, focusing on an engaging experience and ease of use. I am thrilled at the opportunity to apply for this role and a chance to use my skills and experience to contribute in shaping the landscape of music education in the UK.

### **DESIGN PORTFOLIO**

https://twdor.space

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- UX/UI Design
- Figma, Sketch
- Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign
- iOS native components
- Web development
- HTML, CSS, React.js,
- · Wordpress, Wix
- Notion, Jira

- Presentation Skills
- Communication
- Collaboration
- Problem Solving
- Creative thinking
- Attention to detail
- Research Interview skills

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Designer and Developer, WeJam, London, Nov 2021 - present

WeJam is a bootstrapped startup based in Camden that offers an immersive music experience to music fans who would love to play in a band without any musical training.

- Lead WeJam's tablet app re-design, based on user research and recorded user reactions. Created a fresh design system based on the branding guidelines with the aim to create a fun user experience inspired by live music gigs and stage lights.
- Contributed towards the development of a game interface dedicated to helping primary school students learn music in a fun group environment. The UI also featured an accessibility mode for sessions ran in schools for children with special needs.
- Responsible for carrying out improvements and maintenance of the team's Notion for improved project tracking. Creating documentation and team guides and proposing best practice to track internal project progress.
- Set up emailing automations using Zapier, Mailerlite, rclone and Google Drive. Designed follow-up emails in line with the immersive experience and the brand's visual identity.
- Recording and analysing user reactions during the immersive experience and translating them into new features and improvements. Creating developer handoffs for efficient development.
- Creating low and high fidelity wireframes with accurate layout parameters to ensure pixel-perfect designs all the way to deployment.
- Coding in React.js, SCSS and node.js to help with frontend development.
- Coding in Python to automate stages of the music production process

## Freelance Graphic & UX Designer, Remote, May 2022 - present

Provided freelance services for small businesses and individual clients from London, US, and Romania, who offer B2C services in the areas of music teaching, wellbeing and web3.

- Designed the mobile interface for a application that tracks beach volley events and rankings. Used Figma to create reusable components and start populating the platform's design system.
- Designing landing pages in Wordpress and WIX for clients using plugins and custom HTML and CSS styling.
- Designed logos and branding packs for small businesses that successfully communicated the brand message to their target audience.
- Edited and sourced image and video content for engaging marketing campaigns on social media.

## Social Media Assistant, Soundr, London, May 2021 - Jul 2021

Soundr is startup that creates and manages virtual-only artists in the metaverse.

- Creating social media content and initiated early user engagement on Twitter, ahead of NFT releases
- Writing effective copy to connect to the crypto and music Metaverse community on twitter.
- Researching the latest developments in Web3.0 to suggest new content to the team.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **BMus Popular Music, 2.1**

Goldsmiths, University of London Sep 2016 - Jun 2019

Focused on Creative Music Performance and Music Production, ending in a final Degree Performance at the Albany Theatre, Deptford and a Creative Research Project about the potential of music to convey visual content.

## Maths & Computer Science Baccalaureate, 95%

Andrei Sauna National College, Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

- Maths (9.8), ICT (9.5), Physics (9.3)
- Equivalent to A-Levels A\* AA

#### COURSES

- Product Design, Love Circular, 2022
- Digital Skills: User Experience, Certificate by Accenture, Nov 2021, 95%
- SEO Foundations, Linkedin Learning, 2022
- · Advance Your Skills in Graphic Design, Linkedin Learning, currently studying

#### **INTERESTS AND HOBBIES**

I am a singer and songwriter passionate about producing and performing alternative pop. I play guitar, basic keys and always keep an eye out for the latest music industry insights and news. I am also hooked onto learning about innovative technologies, and especially the huge impact AI will have in the creative industries and education. I also always play tennis on weekends.